export const easy = [
  {
    question: "Which symbol is used to end a statement in C?",
    options: [".", ":", ";", ","],
    answer: ";"
  },
  {
    question: "Which function is used to print text in C?",
    options: ["printf()", "echo()", "print()", "cout<<"],
    answer: "printf()"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the correct file extension for C programs?",
    options: [".c", ".cpp", ".java", ".cs"],
    answer: ".c"
  },
  {
    question: "Which header file is used for input/output in C?",
    options: ["<conio.h>", "<stdio.h>", "<stdlib.h>", "<iostream.h>"],
    answer: "<stdio.h>"
  },
  {
    question: "What data type is used to store whole numbers?",
    options: ["float", "int", "char", "double"],
    answer: "int"
  }
];

export const medium = [
  {
    question: "Which loop is guaranteed to run at least once?",
    options: ["for", "while", "do-while", "none"],
    answer: "do-while"
  },
  {
    question: "What does `scanf()` function do?",
    options: ["Displays output", "Takes input", "Loops", "Exits program"],
    answer: "Takes input"
  },
  {
    question: "Which operator is used for logical AND?",
    options: ["&", "&&", "|", "||"],
    answer: "&&"
  },
  {
    question: "How do you define a constant in C?",
    options: ["constant", "const", "#define", "let"],
    answer: "#define"
  },
  {
    question: "Which keyword is used to return a value from a function?",
    options: ["send", "exit", "return", "output"],
    answer: "return"
  }
];

export const hard = [
  {
    question: "Which memory class is used for dynamic allocation?",
    options: ["auto", "register", "heap", "stack"],
    answer: "heap"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the size of `int` in most 64-bit systems?",
    options: ["2 bytes", "4 bytes", "8 bytes", "Depends on compiler"],
    answer: "4 bytes"
  },
  {
    question: "Which keyword is used to prevent modification of a variable?",
    options: ["const", "readonly", "static", "volatile"],
    answer: "const"
  },
  {
    question: "Which function releases dynamically allocated memory?",
    options: ["free()", "delete()", "release()", "remove()"],
    answer: "free()"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the output of 5 % 2 in C?",
    options: ["2.5", "2", "1", "0"],
    answer: "1"
  }
];
